{
    "id": "99f958c7b9d24773a20ae96e210e2cb6",
    "title": "Perfect Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We .................................. in this city since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "lived",
                "have lived"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1964bf09da28417a93cad7cd801fee7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom ................................. with us for ten years before he joined another company.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "had worked",
                "has worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "863c48ef80cd404aaaac2da25c31de39"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long ........................................ with your current employer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you working",
                "have you been working",
                "were you working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bac324bd98f24a98aa16df8fda43c07f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................................... that novel ten times in my life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "have read",
                "am reading"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fe73bb7e5f4d4f1b8a96971bc6a4a65a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................... him for ten years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knew",
                "know",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0705a083871c4bccb0a7dea347220119"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have known him for several years. I first ................................... him in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "met",
                "have met"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f227267859614e3caeafd34423eeb60b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where have you been since I last ................................ you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "saw",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a6a1cda3411f4074972087dfacd81f16"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ..................................... to be an actor since she was a child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wanted",
                "has wanted",
                "wants"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1a6c09e7700d4a0dad9139af87241904"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................................... to London in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a840480eac4648718f2ac4ec85d44e75"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................................. in three films. Her first film came in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "acted",
                "has acted",
                "acts"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d867880fa84a4e599cb70533ff1fc763"
        }
    ]
}